senheng.com.my 2017-11-01

# Privacy Notice | Senheng

This privacy notice explains how we, Senheng Electric (KL) Sdn. Bhd (Company No. 296691-X) process your personal data.

1.    Membership Programme

When you join our membership programme, you will or have provided us with your personal data. Such personal data may include your name, identity card number, contact details, data date of birth, gender, marital status, nationality, preferred language, occupation and monthly income and financial information.

It is mandatory for you to provide us with your name, identity card number, contact details, datae of birth and gender and if you do not provide us with any of this information, we will not process your application or have complete information about you and may affect our membership service to you. We also process other personal data such as your purchasing habits.

We will be processing your personal data for the following purposes:-  
•    evaluating your application to be our member; and  
•    provision of subsequent services such administer the membership programme and benefits such as extended warranty and insurance, customer service, collection of payments from you and issuance of customer vouchers.

2.    Contests

When you join our contests, we will be processing personal data such as name, identity card, address, contact details and signature. It is mandatory for you to provide the required information failing which we will not be able to process your application to join our contest. We will process your personal data to facilitate your participation in our contests.

Periodically, we will organise contests. If you participate in these contests, we reserve the right to publish and/or use the above mentioned personal data for the purpose of advertisements, commerce and publicity whether online and/or offline. Your personal data may also be published on our website if you are one of the winners. We will never distribute your personal data to a third-party for financial gains

3.    Website and Portal

When you register for an account or use the services provided through our electronic portal such as www.senheng.com.my ("Portal"), we will be processing your personal data such as your name, email address, identity card number, contact detail, billing information and some demographic information such as gender and date of birth. It is mandatory for you to provide us with your name, identity card number, contact information and email address to register for an account and also to use our services.

We will process your personal data for the following purposes:-

•    to register an account with us;  
•    to process your orders and order fulfillment.  
•    to provide a more personalized experience on our Portal.

We may correct or supplement your address information with standardized postal representation in order to ensure that your orders are delivered. We do this since we want to make sure that our members receive the order and to lower costs associated with our programs.

When you visit our Portal, we automatically log your internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type and your access times. We utilize this information to conduct site performance evaluations, to see where visitors are coming from and to keep track of click stream data (the screens our users visit on our site). This data helps us to determine what content our members find most appealing so that we can maximize your enjoyment of the sitePortal. Log files are not tied to personally identifiable information.

Your demographic information (gender, date of birth, etc.) will be used for several security purposes, to ensure you are who you say you are and in fact you are paying with your credit cards and not someone using your stolen credit cards.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We do not store this information and uses it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

From time to time we may send out messages alerting you that products are available, to remind you about providing feedback or for promotional offers. In addition, you will receive communication from us 1) if you contact us for a particular reason, 2) to receive your orders, or 3) we need to contact you for administrative purposes such as winning a contest. Administrative e-mails will not contain promotional materials. If you choose to receive our News newslLetters, they will contain promotional materials from our Portal.

We may use session cookies to provide a seamless experience on the site Portal and to combine with our log files so that we can understand our site traffic and analyze our demographic information in aggregate form. Cookies are pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer's hard drive which identify you when you enter the Portal. The ability to select samples on our site is not cookie-driven. If you have set your browser to reject cookies, our site Portal will not identify you when you enter and you will need to manually type in your ID and password.

We may also collect information about you in connection with social networking sites. When you interact with our social networking pages such as Facebook, Twitter and YouTube, we may collect personal data such as your name, nickname and comments. We may use the information we collected about you for the purposes listed at paragraph 4 below.  
      
4.    Other Purposes

Other than the purposes stated above, we will generally process your personal data:-

•    for fulfilment purposes;  
•    for research, statistical, data matching and product development; and  
•    to communicate with you for all the above purposes.

5.    Disclosure

Your personal data will also be disclosed to individuals, service providers and organisations associated with us and any other selected parties (within or outside Malaysia) for all the purposes stated above.

We will also disclose your personal data to any other party to whom such disclosure is required by law or regulatory requirement or pursuant to a Court order. If we are merged or acquired by another entity, the personal data may be transferred to such entity as a part of the merger or acquisition.

6.    Marketing

Unless you opt-out, we will process your personal data for present and future marketing purposes. If you have opted to be contacted for these purposes, We may contact you by way of telephone, electronic communications or by post.

We mainly communicate with you through email, if you wish to unsubscribe the direct marketing communications, you can find and click on the unsubscribe link in each of the promotional email, and we will opt you out from the mailing listing without any cost.

7.    Contacting Us

If you would like to make any inquiries or complaints or request access or correction of the personal data or opt out from receiving direct marketing materials, please contact us at:-

Customer Service  
Address: 44B, Jalan Pandan 3/2, Pandan Jaya, 55100 Kuala Lumpur  
Tel : 03-9281 4040  
Email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

As a a subscriber of our Portal, you may correct or update your personal data by clicking on the 'My Account' link at the top of any page, entering your ID, password and birth date when prompted and clicking the Edit Information button. The changes you make will be reflected in our databases instantly. If you wish to deactivate your account, you may contact our member services group through the 'My Account' section, or the 'Contact Us' section.

Any request of access or correction of personal data may be subject to a fee and also to any privacy or data protection laws. Where you elect to limit our right to process the personal data, you may contact us in writing. For avoidance of doubt, the limitation does not include processing of mandatory personal data.

We have the right to amend the Privacy Notice at any time and if we do so, we will post those changes on our website www.senheng.com.my. By continuing to be our member or using our services, you are deemed to have accepted to the changes.  

Dated: December 2014
